It's said that long ago
Uzun zaman önce
A human samurai once stumbled across the Mikawa Flower Festival
insan bir samuray, bir keresinde Mikawa Çiçek Festivaline rastladı.
What's a human doing here?
Bir insanın burada işi ne?
We erected the barrier, didn't we? Ugh, what a pain...
Bir bariyer kurmuştuk, öyle değil mi? Of, tam bir baş belası...
The youkai at the festival began discussing
Festivaldeki Youkailer, bu insanı
How to drive away the human
nasıl kovacaklarını tartışmaya başladılar.
When suddenly, they heard a voice
Birdenbire bir ses duydular.
This is our festival, and the point is to have fun!
Bu bizim festivalimiz, amacımız da eğlenmek!
What difference does it make if a human joins us youkai!?
Bir insan, biz Youkailere katılsa ne fark eder ki?
The speaker appeared to be a prominent figure among the youkai
Konuşmacı, Youkailer arasında önemli birine benziyordu.
And when he spoke, the other youkai fell silent
O konuşurken etrafındaki Youkailer susuyordu.
You there, young man. Do you drink sake?
Genç adam, sen sake içer misin?
...Yes, I do
Evet, içerim.
Hah! Then join us. We can enjoy tonight's festivities together. Haha!
Hah! O halde bize katıl. Gecenin şenliğinin keyfini birlikte çıkaralım. Haha!
And so, the youkai and samurai celebrated together
Böylece Youkai ile samuray, şenliği birlikte kutladı.
The two competed in the highlight of the festival: the Akitsu Hazura (Haneasobi)
İkisi de festivalin gözdesi olan Akitsu Hazura'da (Haneasobi) rekabet ettiler.
Haha, I can't believe a human could keep up with me
Haha, bir insanın benimle rekabet edebileceğini hiç düşünmemiştim.
Witnessing the dynamic powers of the youkai
Youkailerin gücüne şahit olmanın
Will certainly help hone my swordsmanship
kılıç ustalığı becerilerimi geliştireceğinden eminim.
You're a swordsman!?
Sen bir kılıç ustası mısın?
Yes, I'm currently traveling the world in search of formidable opponents
Evet, şimdi de zorlu rakipler bulmak için dünyayı dolaşıyorum.
Then let's make a deal
O halde bir anlaşma yapalım.
We meet for a duel every ten years, whaddya say?
Her on yılda bir düello yapmak için buluşacağız, ne dersin?
I look forward to it
İple çekiyorum.